David Sapiro

San Francisco, CA • dsap48@gmail.com • 414-405-0017

Summary

Accountant with about 7 years accounting experience looking to transition into a software engineering role. I bring an ability and desire to learn and problem solve as well as to build strong relationships with my team and cross-functional partners. I believe the professional experience in my background in addition to the engineering experience gained through Rithm School make me a great candidate.

Experience

CALIFORNIA ACADEMY OF SCIENCES

San Francisco, CA

Senior Accountant

February 2021 – January 2024

- Reviews all incoming donations for conditions and restrictions in accordance with ASU 2018-08
- Advised development department on relevant accounting guidance, budget coding, and donor campaigns
- Prepared and reviewed schedule and flux analyses for quarterly financial statements
- Prepared over 30 month-end close tasks and journal entries during 5 day close period
- Coordinated with internal and external business partners to facilitate the entire accounts receivable cycle

SCRIBNER COHEN, AND COMPANY, S.C.

Milwaukee, WI

Supervisor Senior Accountant January 2019 – August 2019

June 2018 – December 2018

Staff Accountant

January 2016 - May 2018

- Reviewed or prepared over 130 individual, fiduciary, and business tax returns during tax season
- Researched and summarized complex tax issues for internal memos and client communications
- Analyzed tax returns, bank statements, and financial statements in support of divorce litigation
- Consulted with small business clients on operations, general ledger accounting, and tax issues

Guaranty Bank Milwaukee, WI
Internal Audit Intern May – August 2015

- Performed audits of retail banking branches ensuring all procedures were followed
 - Completed tests of internal controls
 - Reviewed general ledger account reconciliations
 - Audited the estimated liability recorded for loan repurchases

Education

Rithm SchoolSan Francisco, CA
Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp
2024

University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee

Milwaukee, WI

Master of Science, Management-Professional Accounting

2017

Bachelor of Business Administration, Accounting

2016

Cumulative GPA: 4.0

Spring 2016 Lubar School of Business Top Graduating Senior

Skills

Coding languages: HTML, CSS, C, JavaScript

Skills & Qualities: client service, excellent written and verbal communication, time management and prioritization of tasks, deadline oriented, attention to detail